{
    "subject": "resource/William_Petty",
    "predicate": "ontology/influenced",
    "object": "resource/Bernard_Mandeville",
    "human_readable": "William Petty was influenced by Bernard Mandeville.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9652831554412842,
            "question": "Did William Petty acknowledge Bernard Mandeville's influence on his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9484065175056458,
            "question": "How significant was Bernard Mandeville's influence on William Petty's overall body of work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9363893270492554,
            "question": "How did Bernard Mandeville's work impact William Petty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8937431573867798,
            "question": "Were William Petty and Bernard Mandeville contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8859255909919739,
            "question": "Who influenced William Petty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7651353478431702,
            "question": "What were the primary areas of study shared by William Petty and Bernard Mandeville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7384127974510193,
            "question": "Can you name other individuals who were influenced by Bernard Mandeville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6134891510009766,
            "question": "Did William Petty's work share any similarities with Bernard Mandeville's ideas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5088998079299927,
            "question": "What was Bernard Mandeville known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.010486518032848835,
            "question": "What can we learn about the intellectual climate of their time from this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=William Petty was influenced by Bernard Mandeville.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7762_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Bernard Mandeville known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7762_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did William Petty's work share any similarities with Bernard Mandeville's ideas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7762_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other individuals who were influenced by Bernard Mandeville?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7762_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7762_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7762/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt, it is stated that Mandeville was influenced by William Petty's political arithmetic."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context mentions that Bernard Mandeville had a significant influence on prior economists, including William Petty. Specifically, the text states, \"He was also heavily influenced by prior economists, especially William Petty,\" which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of William Petty being influenced by Bernard Mandeville in the provided text.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}